Guide to the American Business Consultants, Inc. Counterattack: Research Files TAM 148
Tamiment Library / Wagner Archives
- Series 9: Individuals, Organizations, Topics, Miscellaneous (arranged by file number)
  - *K. Baarslag (O), undated (Box 6, Folder 9-1050-1051)
  - *K. Baarslag (P), undated (Box 6, Folder 9-1052-1079)
  - *K. Baarslag (P), undated (Box 6, Folder 9-1080-1084)
  - *K. Baarslag (P), undated (Box 6, Folder 9-1085-1090)
  - *K. Baarslag (Philbrick, Herbert), undated (Box 6, Folder 9-1091)
  - *K. Baarslag (P), undated (Box 6, Folder 9-1092-1100)
  - *K. Baarslag (P), undated (Box 7, Folder 9-1101-1105)
  - *K. Baarslag (Q - R), undated (Box 7, Folder 9-1106-1168)
  - *K. Baarslag (Raskin, Marcus G.), 1970 (Box 7, Folder 9-1123)
  - *K. Baarslag (R), undated (Box 7, Folder 9-1169-1179)
  - *K. Baarslag (R), undated (Box 7, Folder 9-1180-1190)
  - *K. Baarslag (R), undated (Box 7, Folder 9-1191-1202)
  - *K. Baarslag (S), undated (Box 7, Folder 9-1023-1263)
  - *K. Baarslag (S), undated (Box 7, Folder 9-1264-1278)
  - *K. Baarslag (Seeger, Pete), undated (Box 7, Folder 9-1275)
  - Missing folders (14), undated (Box 7, Folder 9-1279-1292)
  - Kerry, John, 1971 (Box 7, Folder 9-1293)
  - Ellsberg, Daniel, undated (Box 7, Folder 9-1294)
  - +Jewish Defense League/Meir Kahane, undated (Box 7, Folder 9-1295)
  - Dr. Benjamin Spock, 1965-1972 (Box 7, Folder 9-1296)
  - Soviet Intelligence (R. Michaelowski), undated (Box 7, Folder 9-1297)
  - Missing folder, undated (Box 7, Folder 9-1298)
  - Vietnam Veterans Against the War (VVAW), 1972 (Box 7, Folder 9-1299)
  - Communism, clippings (China, USSR), 1972 (Box 7, Folder 9-1300a)
  - Communism, clippings (China, USSR), 1972-1973 (Box 7, Folder 9-1300b)
  - Our Sunday Visitor, 1966 (Box 7, Folder 9-1301)
  - Socialist Workers Party, 1966 (Box 7, Folder 9-1302)
  - +Patriotic Party (Minutemen), 1967-1968 (Box 7, Folder 9-1303)
  - New Pioneer, 1966 (Box 7, Folder 9-1304)
  - Commentary, 1966-1968 (Box 7, Folder 9-1305)
  - Dissent, 1966 (Box 7, Folder 9-1306)
  - Herbert Aptheker, 1966 (Box 7, Folder 9-1307)
  - Success(Constitutional Alliance), 1966-1967 (Box 7, Folder 9-1808)
  - Despite Everything, 1966 (Box 7, Folder 9-1309)
  - Commonweal, 1966 (Box 7, Folder 9-1310)
  - American Mercury, 1966-1967 (Box 7, Folder 9-1311)
  - Idea Catalyst, 1966 (Box 7, Folder 9-1312)
  - Jane Fonda, 1972 (Box 7, Folder 9-1313)
  - Conference of Socialist Scholars, 1965-1967 (Box 7, Folder 9-1314)
  - Indian affairs (U.S.), 1972 (Box 7, Folder 9-1315)
  - Students for a Democratic Society (SDS), 1966 (Box 7, Folder 9-1316)
  - SDS, 1967-1972 (Box 7, Folder 9-1316)
  - War Resisters League, undated (Box 7, Folder 9-1317)
  - New School for Social Research, 1966 (Box 7, Folder 9-1318)
  - Glenn W. Turner, 1972 (Box 7, Folder 9-1319)
  - People's Party, 1972 (Box 7, Folder 9-1320)
  - *The Reuther Memorandum, 1962 (Box 7, Folder 9-1321)
  - Radical Education Project (SDS), 1966-1968 (Box 7, Folder 9-1322)
  - Labor News and Views, 1965-1966 (Box 7, Folder 9-1323)
  - Global Views, 1966 (Box 7, Folder 9-1324)
  - National Conference for New Politics, 1966-1968 (Box 8, Folder 9-1325)
  - Staughton Lynd, 1965 (Box 8, Folder 9-1326)
  - Eugene Genovese, 1965-1966 (Box 8, Folder 9-1327)
  - Bettina Aptheker, 1965-1967 (Box 8, Folder 9-1328)
  - United Farm Workers Union, 1972 (Box 8, Folder 9-1329)
  - Catalyst, 1966 (Box 8, Folder 9-1330)
  - University Bookman, 1966 (Box 8, Folder 9-1331)
  - Berkeley (CA) Riots, 1964-1967 (Box 8, Folder 9-1332)
  - Fellowship of Reconciliation (FOR), 1966-1967 (Box 8, Folder 9-1333)
  - The Peacemaker, 1966-1967 (Box 8, Folder 9-1334)
  - Our Generation(Montreal), 1966-1968 (Box 8, Folder 9-1335)
  - Alternatives, 1967 (Box 8, Folder 9-1336)
  - CARIB(Caribbean Anti-Communist Research Intelligence Bureau), 1967 (Box 8, Folder 9-1337)
  - MANAS, 1966 (Box 8, Folder 9-1338)
  - Communist Affairs(UCLA), undated (Box 8, Folder 9-1339)
  - Freedom (Press), 1967 (Box 8, Folder 9-1340)
  - Anarchy, 1967 (Box 8, Folder 9-1341)
  - No Tax for War Committee (empty folder), undated (Box 8, Folder 9-1342)
  - Labor Today(Trade Union Action Democracy - CPUSA sponsored), 1967 (Box 8, Folder 9-1343)
  - N.Y. Federation of Anarchists, undated (Box 8, Folder 9-1344)
  - + Viewpoint(Florida League for Good Government), 1967 (Box 8, Folder 9-1345)
  - American Atheist, 1967 (Box 8, Folder 9-1346)
  - War/Peace Report, undated (Box 8, Folder 9-1347)
  - Florida Folk Foundation, 1967 (Box 8, Folder 9-1348)
  - Protective Bulletin, 1967 (Box 8, Folder 9-1349)
  - The Activist, 1967-1969 (Box 8, Folder 9-1350)
  - Committee of 100 in Support of NAACP Legal Defense & Educational Fund, 1967-1968 (Box 8, Folder 9-1351)
  - Sing Out, 1967-1968 (Box 8, Folder 9-1352)
  - The Independent(Miami), 1967-1968 (Box 8, Folder 9-1353)
  - Ad-Hoc Bulletin(Marxist-Leninist), 1967 (Box 8, Folder 9-1354)
  - +Mothers of Servicemen, 1967 (Box 8, Folder 9-1355)
  - Women Strike for Peace (WSP), 1962-1967 (Box 8, Folder 9-1356)
  - Stokely Carmichael, 1966-1971 (Box 8, Folder 9-1357)
  - Tri-Continental Conference (Havana, 1966), 1966-1967 (Box 8, Folder 9-1358)
  - (pg# 1-135 ) Organization for Latin American Security (OLAS), 1966-1967 (Box 8, Folder 9-1358A)
  - (pg# 136-246 ) OLAS, 1967 (Box 8, Folder 9-1358A)
  - Cuba - Cultural Congress (1968), 1967-1968 (Box 8, Folder 9-1358B)
  - +Carl McIntyre, 1971 (Box 8, Folder 9-1359)
  - Tampa Riots of 1967 (Box 8, Folder 9-1360)
  - SLAM(Newsletter of the Southern Labor Action Movement), 1967 (Box 8, Folder 9-1361)
  - Black Power, 1966-1968 (Box 8, Folder 9-1362)
  - Daily World, 1968-1969 (Box 8, Folder 9-1363)
  - RAM (Revolutionary Action Movement), 1967 (Box 8, Folder 9-1364)
  - Adam Clayton Powell, 1964-1971 (Box 8, Folder 9-1365)
  - Joan Baez, 1963-1971 (Box 8, Folder 9-1366)
  - H. Rap Brown, 1967-1971 (Box 8, Folder 9-1367)
  - Dick Gregory, 1963-1969 (Box 8, Folder 9-1368)
  - James Meredith, 1963-1968 (Box 8, Folder 9-1369)
  - Missing Folders (30), undated (Box 8, Folder 9-1370 -- 9-1399)
  - *K. Baarslag (S), undated (Box 8, Folder 9-1400-1406)
  - *K. Baarslag (S - T), undated (Box 8, Folder 9-1407-1437)
  - *K. Baarslag (T - V), undated (Box 8, Folder 9-1438-1509)
  - *K. Baarslag (V - W), undated (Box 8, Folder 9-1510-1523)
  - *K. Baarslag (W), undated (Box 9, Folder 9-1524-1537)
  - *K. Baarslag (W), undated (Box 9, Folder 9-1538-1571)
  - *K. Baarslag (W), undated (Box 9, Folder 9-1572-1599)
  - *K. Baarslag (X - Z), undated (Box 9, Folder 9-1600-1620)
  - Puerto Rico(Comandos Armados de Liberacion), 1968 (Box 9, Folder 9-1621)
  - Youth International Party (Yippies), 1968-1969 (Box 9, Folder 9-1622)
  - *United Electrical, Radio and Machine Workers Union (UE), undated (Box 9, Folder no#)
  - David Mortimer Livingston, report on, 1953 (Box 9, Folder no#)
  - Robert Burke (alias William Burke), report on - District 65, 1953 (Box 9, Folder no#)
  - Jack Paley (District 65 Secy-Treas), report on, 1953 (Box 9, Folder no#)
- Series 10: Countries.
  - Argentina, 1946-1967 (Box 9, Folder 10-1)
  - Australia, 1947-1949 (Box 9, Folder 10-2)
  - Austria, 1946-1947 (Box 9, Folder 10-3)
  - Brazil, 1946-1948 (Box 9, Folder 10-4)
  - Chile, 1946-1949 (Box 9, Folder 10-5)
  - China, 1945 (Box 9, Folder 10-6-I)
  - China, 1949 (Box 9, Folder 10-6-II)
  - Czechoslovakia, 1946-1949 (Box 9, Folder 10-7)
  - England, 1946-1949 (Box 9, Folder 10-8)
  - Far East, 1946-1949 (Box 9, Folder 10-9)
  - France, 1938-???? (Box 9, Folder 10-10)
  - Germany, 1945-1955 (Box 10, Folder 10-11)
  - Hungary, 1946-1949 (Box 10, Folder 10-12)
  - Iran, 1944-1949 (Box 10, Folder 10-13)
  - Italy, 1946-1949 (Box 10, Folder 10-14)
  - Japan, 1946-1949 (Box 10, Folder 10-15)
  - Poland, 1942-1948 (Box 10, Folder 10-16)
  - Romania, 1944-1948 (Box 10, Folder 10-17)
  - (pg# 1-114 ) Russia, 1939-1946 (Box 10, Folder 10-18)
  - (pg# 115-201 ) Russia, 1946-1947 (Box 10, Folder 10-18)
  - (pg# 202-? ) Russia, 1945-1949 (Box 10, Folder 10-18)
  - Russia, 1948-1949 (Box 10, Folder 10-18A)
  - Russia, undated (Box 10, Folder 10-18B)
  - "Russian Journal" (John Steinbeck, Robert Capa), 1948 (Box 10, Folder 10-18C)
  - Yugoslavia, 1946-1949 (Box 10, Folder 10-19)
  - UNRRA (United Nations Relief & Rehabilitation Admin), 1946-1947 (Box 10, Folder 10-20)
  - United Nations, 1946-1952 (Box 10, Folder 10-22)
  - Maps of Europe, 1946 (Box 10, Folder 10-23)
  - Greece, 1944-1949 (Box 10, Folder 10-32)
  - Canada, 1948-1949 (Box 10, Folder 10-46)
  - India, 1946-1949 (Box 10, Folder 10-60)
  - Hawaiian Islands, 1947-1949 (Box 10, Folder 10-90)
  - (Box 10)
  - CP - leaders, officials, individuals, 1939-1953 (Box 10, Folder 11-0-1)
- Series 11: Communist Party of the United States of America
  - CP: Counterattack File System, 1946 (Box 11, Folder 11-0, Box 10)
  - CP: Leaders, Officials, Individuals, 1939-1953 (Box 10, Folder 11-0-1, Box 11)
  - CP: Proceedings of Eastern Seabord Conference, 1947 (Box 11, Folder 11-0-A, Box 10)
  - CP, 1939-1949 (Box 10, Folder 11-1, Box 11)
  - CP, 1948-1949 (Box 11, Folder 11-1A,v1, Box 10, Folder 11-1A.v1)
  - CP: Trial of the 11, 1949 (Box 10, Folder 11-1A.v2, Box 11)
  - CP: Districct 1 (MA, ME, NH, RI, VT), 1948 (Box 10, Folder 11-2, Box 11)
  - CP: District 2 (New York State), 1942-1948 (Box 10, Folder 11-3, Box 11)
  - CP: Bronx, New York, 1946-1947 (Box 10, Folder 11-3A, Box 11)
  - CP: Brooklyn, New York, 1939-1947 (Box 10, Folder 11-3B, Box 11)
  - CP: Manhattan, New York, 1945-1947 (Box 10, Folder 11-3C, Box 11)
  - CP: Queens, New York, 1938-1946 (Box 10, Folder 11-3D, Box 11)
  - CP: Queens, New York, 1943-1947 (Box 10, Folder 11-3D.v2, Box 11)
  - CP: Upstate, New York, 1946-1947 (Box 10, Folder 11-3E, Box 11)
  - CP: District 3 (empty folder), undated (Box 11, Folder 11-4, Box 10)
  - CP: District 4 (Washington, DC and Maryland), 1946-1953 (Box 10, Folder 11-5)
  - CP: District 5 (empty folder), undated (Box 11, Folder 11-6, Box 10)
  - CP: District 6 (Ohio), 1940 (Box 11, Folder 11-7)
  - CP: District 8 (Michigan), 1940-1948 (Box 11, Folder 11-8)
  - CP: District 8 (Illinois, Indiana, Kentucky), 1940-1950 (Box 11, Folder 11-9)
  - CP: District 9 (Minnesota, North and South Dakota), 1940-1961 (Box 11, Folder 11-10)
  - CP: District 12 (Washington, Oregon, Idaho), 1946-1947 (Box 11, Folder 11-11)
  - CP: District 13 (California, Arizona, Nevada), 1940-1951 (Box 11, Folder 11-12)
  - CP: District 14 (New Jersey), 1940-`949 (Box 11, Folder 11-13)
  - CP: District 15 (empty folder), undated (Box 11, Folder 11-14)
  - CP: District 18 (Wisconsin), 1940-1946 (Box 11, Folder 11-15)
  - CP: District 19 (empty folder), undated (Box 11, Folder 11-16)
  - CP: District 21 (empty folder), undated (Box 11, Folder 11-17)
  - CP: District 22 (empty folder), undated (Box 11, Folder 11-18)
  - CP: Districct 23 (Texas), 1952 (Box 11, Folder 11-19)
  - CP: District 24 (Louisiana), 1946 (Box 11, Folder 11-20)
  - CP: District 25 (empty folder), undated (Box 11, Folder 11-21)
  - CP: District 26 (Virginia, North and South Carolina), 1947 (Box 11, Folder 11-22)
  - CP: District 27 (Alabama, Georgia, Mississippi, Tennessee), 1946 (Box 11, Folder 11-23)
  - CP: District 28 (Arkansas, Oklahoma), 1940 (Box 11, Folder 11-24)
  - CP: District 30 (empty folder), undated (Box 11, Folder 11-25)
  - CP: District 32-35 (Nebraska, Iowa, Kansas, Utah), 1940 (Box 11, Folder 11-26)
  - CP: International, 1939-1947 (Box 11, Folder 11-27)
  - Comintern, 1947 (Box 11, Folder 11-27A)
  - CP: Culture, 1946 (Box 11, Folder 11-28)
  - CP: Government Employees, 1940-1947 (Box 12, Folder 11-29, Box 11)
  - CP: Ideology, 1938-1946 (Box 12, Folder 11-30, Box 11)
  - CP: Jews, 1946-1947 (Box 12, Folder 11-31, Box 11)
  - CP: Negroes, 1939-1947 (Box 12, Folder 11-32, Box 11)
  - CP: The Professions, 1946-1947 (Box 12, Folder 11-33, Box 11)
  - CP: Publications, 1943-1949 (Box 12, Folder 11-34, Box 11)
  - CP: Daily Worker, 1939-1949 (Box 11, Folder 11-34A, Box 12)
  - DP: Daily Worker: Index of Photographs, 1922-1942, undated (Box 11, Folder 11-34Asup, Box 12)
  - CP: Daily Worker Abstracts, Jan 1, 1935-Jun 23, 1941 (Box 11, Folder 11-34B, Box 12)
  - CP: Tactics, 1938-1948 (Box 12, Folder 11-35)
  - CP: Youth, 1940-1952 (Box 12, Folder 11-36)
  - CP: Veterans, 1946-1947 (Box 12, Folder 11-37)
  - CP: Education, 1940-1953 (Box 12, Folder 11-38)
  - CP: Organization, 1945-1947 (Box 12, Folder 11-39)
  - CP: Trade Unions, 1945-1947 (Box 12, Folder 11-40)
  - CP: Elections, 1946 (Box 12, Folder 11-41)
  - CP: Religion, 1948-1953 (Box 12, Folder 11-42)
  - CP: South, 1948 (Box 12, Folder 11-43)
  - CP: Radio, 1947 (Box 12, Folder 11-44)
  - CP: Party Lines, 1953 (Box 12, Folder 11-45)
  - CP: Food Industry, 1949 (Box 12, Folder 11-46)
  - CP: New York State Convention Proceedingss, Jul 16, 1948-Jul 18, 1948 (Box 12, Folder 11-47)
  - CP: National Convention Proceedings, Aug 3, 1948-Aug 4, 1948 (Box 12, Folder 11-48)
  - CP: Laws and Bills Affecting, 1948-1950 (Box 12, Folder 11-49)
- Series 12: Communist Party, USA Front Organizations.
  - Master List of Front Organizations, undated (Box 13, Folder 12-0)
  - Fronts-miscellaneous, 1947-1950 (Box 13, Folder 12-)
  - (pg# 1-46 ) Fronts-miscellaneous, 1942-1947 (Box 13, Folder 12-0-A)
  - (pg# 47-84 ) Fronts-miscellaneous, 1945-1948 (Box 13, Folder 12-0-B)
  - (pg# 85-163 ) Fronts-miscellaneous, 1946-1953 (Box 13, Folder 12-0-C)
  - (pg# 3-42 ) Fronts-miscellaneous, 1944-1953 (Box 13, Folder 12-0-1A)
  - (pg# 1-37 ) United Committee for South-Slavic Americans; American Slav Congress; American Association for Reconstruction in Yugoslavia, 1944-1949 (Box 13, Folder 12-1-1)
  - (pg# 1-12 ) American Birobidjan Committee, 1942-1948 (Box 13, Folder 12-2)
  - (pg# 1-15 ) American Committee for Armenian Rights, 1945-1947 (Box 13, Folder 12-3)
  - (pg# 1-30 ) Committee for a Democratic Far Eastern Policy, 1946-1947 (Box 13, Folder 12-4-v.I)
  - (pg# 31-65 ) Committee for a Democratic Far Eastern Policy, 1947-1949 (Box 13, Folder 12-4-v.I)
  - (pg# 66-91 ) Committee for a Democratic Far Eastern Policy, 1948-1949 (Box 13, Folder 12-4-v.I)
  - (pg# 92-103 ) Committee for a Democratic Far Eastern Policy, 1948-1950 (Box 13, Folder 12-4-v.II)
  - (pg# 1-20 ) Committee for a Democratic Far Eastern Policy, 1947-1949 (Box 13, Folder 12-4-1A-v.I)
  - (pg# 21-27 ) Committee for a Democratic Far Eastern Policy, 1948-1949 (Box 13, Folder 12-4-1A-v.II)
  - (pg# 1-53 ) American Labor Party, 1939-1948 (Box 13, Folder 12-5-v.I)
  - (pg# 54-115 ) American Labor Party, 1940-1949 (Box 13, Folder 12-5-v.II)
  - (pg# 1-51 ) Civil Rights Congress, 1938-1948 (Box 13, Folder 12-7-v.I)
  - (pg# 6-20 ) Civil Rights Congress, 1940-1949 (Box 13, Folder 12-7-1A-v.I)
  - (pg# 51-78 ) Civil Rights Congress, 1945-1949 (Box 13, Folder 12-7-v.II)
  - (pg# 1-10 ) The Trenton Six, 1949 (Box 13, Folder 12-7A)
  - (pg# 1-23 ) Council on African Affairs, 1946-1948 (Box 13, Folder 12-9)
  - (pg# 1-24 ) Greek-American Council; American Relief for Greek Democracy; American Council for a Democratic Greece, 1946-1947 (Box 13, Folder 12-10)
  - (pg# 1-53 ) Progressive Citizens of America, 1945-1946 (Box 13, Folder 12-11-v.I)
  - (pg# 54-108 ) Progressive Citizens of America, 1945-1947 (Box 13, Folder 12-11-v.II)
  - (pg# 109-123 ) Progressive Citizens of America, 1947-1948 (Box 13, Folder 12-11-v.III)
  - (pg# 1-2 ) Indonesia League of America, 1946 (Box 13, Folder 12-12)
  - (pg# 1-2 ) Workers Personal Service Bureau, undated (Box 13, Folder 12-13)
  - (pg# 1-2 ) National Citizens Emergency Relief Committee to Aid Strikers' Families, 1946 (Box 13, Folder 12-14)
  - (pg# 1-71 ) National Council of American-Soviet Friendship, 1941-1951 (Box 13, Folder 12-15)
  - (pg# 1-13 ) National Council of American-Soviet Friendship, 1941-1949 (Box 13, Folder 12-15-1A)
  - (pg# 1-18 ) National Council of American-Soviet Friendship - Committee of Women, 1949 (Box 13, Folder 12-15A)
  - National Council of American-Soviet Friendship, 1944-1945 (Box 13, Folder 12-15-Sup)
  - (pg# 1-10 ) National Negro Congress, 1941-1947 (Box 13, Folder 12-16)
  - (pg# 2,4 ) National Negro Congress, 1937-1946 (Box 13, Folder 12-16-1A)
  - (pg# 1-7 ) People's Songs/Stage for Action, 1946-1947 (Box 13, Folder 12-17)
  - (pg# 1-42 ) Win the Peace Conference; National Conference to Win the Peace, 1946-1948 (Box 13, Folder 12-18)
  - (pg# 1-4 ) Win the Peace Conference; National Conference to Win the Peace, 1946 (Box 13, Folder 12-18-1A)
  - (pg# 1-12 ) Indusco, Inc. American Committee in Aid of Chinese Industrial Affairs, 1946-1949 (Box 13, Folder 12-19)
  - (pg# 1-5 ) Russian War Relief, Inc.; American Society for Russian Relief, Inc., 1942-1949 (Box 13, Folder 12-20)
  - (pg# 1-11 ) N.Y. Committee for Justice in Freeport, 1946 (Box 13, Folder 12-21)
  - (pg# 1-2 ) Japanese-American Committee for Democracy, 1946-1947 (Box 13, Folder 12-22)
  - (pg# 1-39 ) Schools, 1939-1952 (Box 13, Folder 12-23)
  - (pg# 1-36 ) Schools, 1942-1952 (Box 13, Folder 12-23-1A)
  - (pg# 1-18 ) In Fact, 1945-1951 (Box 14, Folder 12-24)
  - In Fact, 1938-1946 (Box 14, Folder 12-24-1A)
  - (pg# 1-12 ) Trade Union Committee for Jewish Unity (AKA American Jewish Labor Council), 1946-1949 (Box 14, Folder 12-25)
  - undated (Box 14)
  - (pg# 1-14 ) Book Find Club, 1946-1949 (Box 14, Folder 12-26)
  - Book Find Club, 1946 (Box 14, Folder 12-26A)
  - (pg# 1-2 ) Artists: Artists' League of America; Artists Union; American Artists Congress; American Contemporary Artists, undated (Box 14, Folder 12-27-1A)
  - (pg# 1-93 ) Spanish file, 1938-1951 (Box 14, Folder 12-28-v.I)
  - (pg# 1-13 ) Spanish file, 1040-1950 (Box 14, Folder 12-28-1A)
  - (pg# 94-97 ) Spanish file, 1948-1950 (Box 14, Folder 12-28-v.II)
  - (pg# 1-12 ) American Legion, 1945-1946 (Box 14, Folder 12-30)
  - (pg# 1-25 ) The Protestant, 1943-1948 (Box 14, Folder 12-31)
  - (pg# 1-43 ) International Workers Order, 1940-1966 (Box 14, Folder 12-32)
  - (pg# 1-50 ) Political Action Committee, C.I.O., 1944-1946 (Box 14, Folder 12-33)
  - (pg# 1-12 ) Political Action Committee, C.I.O., 1944-1946 (Box 14, Folder 12-33-1A)
  - (pg# 1-29 ) National Citizens Political Action Committee, 1946-1948 (Box 14, Folder 12-33A)
  - National Citizens Political Action Committee, 1946 (Box 14, Folder 12-33B)
  - (pg# 1-34 ) Fronts, Defunct, 1939-1946 (Box 14, Folder 12-34)
  - (pg# 1-37 ) American Peace Mobilization; American Peoples Mobilization (defunct), 1940-1941 (Box 14, Folder 12-35)
  - (pg# 38-101 ) American Peace Mobilization; American Peoples Mobilization (defunct), 1940-1942 (Box 14, Folder 12-35)
  - (pg# 1-12 ) American Peace Mobilization, American Peoples Mobilization (defunct), 1940-1941 (Box 14, Folder 12-35-1A)
  - Veterans Against Discrimination (unprocessed), undated (Box 14, Folder 12-36)
  - Peoples Institute of Applied Religion (unprocessed), undated (Box 14, Folder 12-38)
  - American Youth for Democracy (defunct); Young Communist, undated (Box 14, Folder 12-40)
  - League (defunct) (unprocessed), undated (Box 14)
  - Youth(publication of the American Youth for Democracy) (unprocessed), undated (Box 14, Folder 12-40A)
  - Labor Youth League (unprocessed), undated (Box 14, Folder 12-40B)
  - Austro-American Committee (unprocessed), undated (Box 14, Folder 12-41)
  - American Russian Institute (unprocessed, undated (Box 14, Folder 12-42)
  - American Student Union, 1933-1941 (Box 15, Folder 12-43)
  - American League for Peace and Democracy, 1939-1940 (Box 15, Folder 12-44)
  - American Youth Congress, 1939-1941 (Box 15, Folder 12-45)
  - National Lawyers Guild (NLG), 1948 (Box 15, Folder 12-46)
  - Missing folder, undated (Box 15, Folder 12-47)
  - Missing folder, undated (Box 15, Folder 12-48)
  - Workers' Alliance of America, 1940-1942 (Box 15, Folder 12-49)
  - Fronts - Publications, undated (Box 15, Folder 12-50)
  - *Consumers' Union, 1948 (Box 15, Folder 12-51)
  - Congress of American Women, 1949 (Box 15, Folder 12-52)
  - Young Progressives of America, 1946-1949 (Box 15, Folder 12-53A)
  - (pg# 1-100 ) Progressive Party, 1946-1948 (Box 15, Folder 12-53)
  - (pg# 101-200 ) Progressive Party, undated (Box 15, Folder 12-53)
  - (pg# 201-253 ) Progressive Party, 1949 (Box 15, Folder 21-53)
  - New Council of American Business, Inc., undated (Box 15, Folder 12-54)
  - Progressive Party Petition Signers, Pittsburgh area, 1948 (Box 16, Folder 12-53B)
  - Missing folder, undated (Box 16, Folder 12-54)
  - Missing folder, undated (Box 16, Folder 12-55)
  - Conference of Progressives (Chicago, 1946) (Box 16, Folder 12-56)
  - *American Council - Institute for Pacific Relations, undated (Box 16, Folder 21-57)
  - *American Council - Institute for Pacific Relations, undated (Box 16, Folder 12/57/ Suppl)
  - Federal Council of Churches of Christ in America, undated (Box 16, Folder 12-58)
  - *People's Radio Foundation, undated (Box 16, Folder 12-59)
  - California Labor School, undated (Box 16, Folder 12-60)
  - League of Women Shoppers, undated (Box 16, Folder 12-61)
  - Southern Conference for Human Welfare, undated (Box 16, Folder 12-62)
  - Stop Censorship Committee, 1948 (Box 16, Folder 12-63)
  - American Committee for European Workers' Relief (Missing folder), undated (Box 16, Folder 12-64)
  - United Christian Council for Democracy, 1948 (Box 16, Folder 21-65)
  - *American Committee for Protection of Foreign Born, 1940s-50s (Box 16, Folder 12-66)
  - American Committee for Protection of Foreign Born, undated (Box 16, Folder 12-66/ Suppl)
  - *League for Industrial Democracy, 1948 (Box 16, Folder 12-67)
  - Physicians Forum, Inc., 1948 (Box 16, Folder 12-68)
  - American Committee of Jewish Writers, Artists and Scientists, undated (Box 16, Folder 12-69)
  - Committee of One Thousand, undated (Box 16, Folder 12-70)
  - Committee for Democratic Rights, 1948 (Box 16, Folder 12-71)
  - United World Federalists, 1950 (Box 16, Folder 12-72)
  - *United World Federalists (supplemental), undated (Box 16, Folder 12-72a)
  - *Yale University, 1949 (Box 16, Folder 12-73)
  - *Harvard University, undated (Box 16, Folder 12-73a)
  - New York University, 1949 (Box 16, Folder 12-73b)
  - Film Audiences for Democracy, 1948 (Box 16, Folder 12-74)
  - National Gazette, 1948 (Box 16, Folder 12-75)
  - *Negro Labor Congress, undated (Box 16, Folder 12-76)
  - Sons of Liberty Boycott Committee, 1948 (Box 16, Folder 12-77)
  - *American Friends of India, undated (Box 16, Folder 12-78)
  - *American Veterans of the Philippine Campaign, 1946-1948 (Box 17, Folder 12-79)
  - *Jefferson School of Social Science, 1949-1954 (Box 17, Folder 12-80.v1)
  - Jefferson School of Social Science, 1949-1953 (Box 17, Folder 12-80.v2)
  - *Consumer and Tenant Fronts, 1946-1949 (Box 17, Folder 12-81)
  - United Committee to Save the Jewish State and the United Nations, 1948 (Box 17, Folder 12-82)
  - *World Congress of Intellectuals Affiliate: International Committee in Defense of Peace, 1948 (Box 17, Folder 12-83)
  - Cultural and Scientific Conference for World Peace, 1949 (Box 17, Folder 12-83a)
  - Waldorf Culture Conference Speeches, 1949 (Box 17, Folder 12-83a1)
  - Waldorf Culture Conference Speeches, 1949 (Box 17, Folder 12-83a2)
  - Paris Peace Congress and the American Sponsoring Committee of the World Peace Congress, 1949 (Box 17, Folder 12-83b)
  - American Continental Congress for Peace, 1949 (Box 17, Folder 12-83c)
  - American Jewish Congress, 1946-1965 (Box 17, Folder 12-84)
  - *Intelligence Research Bureau Reports Volume I (1-110), 1948-1949 (Box 17, Folder 12-85.v1)
  - *Intelligence Research Bureau Reports Volume II (111-230), 1949-1950 (Box 17, Folder 12-85.v2)
  - *Intelligence Research Bureau Reports Volume III (231-373), 1950 (Box 17, Folder 12-85.v3)
  - *Intelligence Research Bureau Reports Volume IV (374-441), 1950-1954 (Box 17, Folder 12-85.v4)
  - Scientists' Committee on Loyalty Problems, 1948-1949 (Box 17, Folder 12-86)